Bull's Eye, up!
打靶仔 上去
Throw them down
扔下来
Here's for you
死啦
- Bull's Eye - Tung
- 打靶仔 - 东哥
We've been waiting anxiously.
大家等你等得很焦急呀
- Ah Pan - Tung
- 老彭 - 东哥
Tung, Tung!
东哥 东哥
Tung's bringing us luck
东哥这次回来我们有福了
Tung lights up our lives
见到东哥有如见到阳光呀
Got something for everyone, one each
你们别说东哥偏心 每人一只
- Famous brand - Right
- 是梅球呀 - 对呀
What a difference this time
东哥 这次回来真有天渊之别呀
Chubby, Dupont,
肥姑 这是都彭呀
expensive even in HK
在香港都算是名贵的了
It's yours
给你
- Let me, granny - Alright
- 婆婆 我帮你 - 好
Granny, these abalone are for you from Tung
婆婆 这是青边鲍鱼 东哥送给你的
- Thank you. - How are you, granny?
- 谢谢 - 婆婆 你好吗?
Thanks, granny's too old now, no teeth
谢谢 有牙就好了 几十岁没用啦
You can still eat them
可以吃的 怎么不能呢?
Operation date on Dec. 1 9,
起程的日期是十二月十九号
one month from now
距离现在还有一个月
The trip will take one full day
行程需要一日一夜
Why that day?
我为什么要选择这一天呢?
The 20th is Buddha's Day
因为二十号是弥陀佛诞
It's be easier to get pass the road block
方便你们容易混入九龙
Have you planned the mountain route yet?
肥姑 攀山这条路你研究得怎么样了?
Yes I have We'll get on the train off
在白云宾馆对出的那个弯位
White-Cloud Hotel
扑车最为理想
We'll get to Shung Kong by nine
火车大约在九点多就可到达筍江站
We'll get off at Shung Kong
我们在筍江站马上落车
Cross the hill to Shen Zhen, and the border
跟着攀山过深圳 经菜屋园再攀网
The trip will take 5 hours
最多不会超过五个钟头
We'll get to the border
在天亮之前
before dawn
我们一定可以到达香港边界
Alright
好
I'll be at the Wah Lai Hotel
无论如何二十号那天
on the 20th
我在上水华丽公寓等你们
Call me as soon as you cross the border
你们到了香港马上打电话给我
Here's the phone number and address
这是华丽公寓的电话和地址
If we succeed
这次如果成功的话
Each share worths HK$250,000
每人可分得港币大概有二十五万
Enough for a life time
做死一世也没有这么多呀
HK$100 for $28 our money
现在一百元港币兑二十八元人民币
We're making $50 per month,
我们每个月赚五十元
plus overtime
连加班和奖金在内
At this rate
以我们现在的工资来算
It'll take us 100 years
每人就算做一百年
to make this sum
也不能赚得那么多钱
No wonder they all go to Hong Kong
难怪大沙头那班烂鬼去了香港十几天
And then come back
回来以后每个人都穿得美丽整齐
Ioaded with money
威风凛凛一样
Right,
对 对
and lots of jewelry
还有他们的金链重到连颈都粗了
Golden necklace this thick
这么粗的呀
You must be mentally prepared
你们一定要从思想上做好充份的准备
We need all of our experience
我们要拿出当年攻打中山纪念堂
Every skill we'd learnt
打垮主义兵的劲度
in our army days
打 砸 抢 来搞掂它
48 hours return trip
四十八小时来回
When we get back
返回广州后
we'll retire for good
我们就可以过着一世安乐日子了
48 hours, that's two days
姑哥 四十八小时等于两天
No time for massage parlour
连冲凉敲骨都没有时间
Right,
对
not even time for shopping
一场辛苦到了那儿连想买东西都没空
My wife won't like it.
我就无所谓 最惨的是家中的老婆
Time is precious for security reason
不可能 多留一天就多一分风险
We're going to make money, not to spend it
我带你们去是要发财不是发梦
Anyone disagree
如果有谁人不赞成两日来回的话
Then the operation is cancelled
这个计划就取消
We'll follow Tung's instructions,
我们当然是尊重东哥的的意见
of course
原则上没问题
One for all
总之这次成功的话就吃牛扒
All for one
否则就黄华 坐监了
Great, one for all
好 十二月十九成功就吃牛扒
"That's Eagle Bay, rough water"
前面就是那大鹏湾 波涛汹涌澎湃
"So what? "
可是在我们面前 算得了什么?
"A stream separates two worlds"
一条小河分两个世界 令我心响往
"We'll cross it alright"
只要你不畏那艰险 一定胜利渡河去
One for all, all for one
成功就吃牛扒 不成功就黄华
Cheers...
干杯
May the gods bless them all
求神保佑他们顺风顺水直到尖沙咀
Especially Chubby
特别是我们的肥姑 三代单传
Bless for his return, with money
保佑他平安发财
Blockhead
乌蝇头 乌蝇头
Go home,
早就叫你不要送的了
no need to see me off
大家都说不许送的了
OK, don't cry now, baby
乖乖 让爸爸抱一回 不要哭
I'll bring you
爸爸过两天回来买枝玩具枪给你
a toy gun
好不好?
Don't forget
单子你也忘了拿
the shopping list
这么大的人都没心肝
Send some money when you're there
到了香港就要寄钱回来
Don't cry now
不要哭
Don't get the wrong things
染发素要德国的才好买呀
OK
知道啦
No time for shopping anyway
我们没有什么多余时间去买东西
Take him back
抱回他吧
Wide-rim sun glasses
太阳眼镜要拣阔边的才好买
Something fashionable
样子要让服务员看过 才买呀
Alright,
好啦好啦
I'll bring back the shop
我把整个香港买回来 够了吗?
Don't cry
不要哭 你又哭什么呀?
I won't forget a thing
我说过不会漏买东西的
Be good,
你要生性点呀
think of us
你不挂念我也要挂住个儿子呀
I know those Hong Kong girls
香港的女孩子全是水性杨花
Keep your hands off them
千万不要做出对我们母子不起的事
OK, this is no funeral
知道啦 像送丧一样 回去吧回去吧
- Go, go! - Let's go
- 走吧 走 - 起程啦
Stop complaining
别再啰嗦了
The wire net
网呀
Rooster, seen any Big Cats?
生鸡 听听有没有大猫?
Yeah, Big Cats
有大猫呀
Soldiers, Bull's Eye!
有军佬呀 打靶仔
Don't shoot. Run for it
不要开枪… 没时间了 冲呀
Freeze, don't run
站着 别跑
Stop, or I'll shoot
再跑 他奶奶的熊 我开枪啦
Damn it, do you hear, stop
他奶奶的熊 叫你们别跑听见了没有?
Stop, we're going to shoot
再跑俺开枪毙了你们
You won't make it
你们跑不了啦
Send in the dogs
放狗咬他们 快 放狗
It hurts
好痛呀
Bull's Eye!
打靶仔 打靶仔
Run for it, before it's too late
走吧 快走 不走就没命了
help me, help me!
救救我 救救我
help, help me
救救我 救命呀
What are you to?
你们干什么?
Keep quiet! We're not thieves
阿伯 别出声 我们不是贼
Can I use your phone
想借个电话用用
Please, keep those dogs quiet
阿伯 帮帮忙叫那些狗不要吠呀
Hello, yes, no, no such person
喂 是 不是 没有这个人
Asking for Ho?
阿伯 是不是找姓何的?
Why didn't you say so
明知是找你的又不早说呢
This is no Grand Hotel
你以为这儿是大酒店吗?
Hello, Chubby, how's it going?
喂 肥姑呀?怎么样?
Where are you now?
你们现在在哪里?
Sorry, Tung,
东哥 对不起
couldn't pull Bull's Eye off
打靶仔我帮不了他的忙
Tough luck,
打靶仔倒霉透了
first he hurt his leg
上山的时候弄伤了脚
I knew it's not his day
我已经知道他当黑了
He should've
东哥 打靶仔在起程的时候
prayed to the gods
没有散发溪钱
His own fault
他真是自己作贱自己
Don't cry,
别哭了 现在不是哭的时候
go change
你们快换衣服去
Thanks a lot, old man
阿伯 谢谢你的帮忙
Here's something for you
这儿一点点的钱给你 拿去吧
This is illegal
不要不要 这是犯法的事
Just leave quick
你们快点走 就好了
Cops, the drums
有鬼呀 起鼓
Stop, stop
收鼓 收鼓呀
License please
把牌拿出来
You clowns,
最讨厌是你们这班兔崽子
where's the circus
在这儿胡闹
Why not the
要不要多安装几个喇叭呀
whole orchestra
慢点就会死了吗?
Shut up...ID Card
你…大头鬼 把身份证拿出来
ID card
身份证呀
Who's asking you?
又不是问你 有身份证有什么稀奇?
Sir
阿Sir
It's Buddha's birthday today
阿Sir 对不起 今天是弥陀佛诞
Who cares,
不管是什么玉皇大帝
that's no excuse
总而言之太嘈吵就不行
We'll keep it down
我们会声音小一点的
Got a license
你以为舞狮就了不起了吗?
for the Birthday party?
有没有人情纸呀?
I can arrest you all
信不信我把你们全部抓回去
Whose ID card?
这张身份证是谁的?
Mine, sir, thanks
阿Sir 是我的 谢谢你
Fatty, from here on
小胖 由现在开始一直到市区
No more drum beating, right?
不许再打锣打鼓 嘈嘈吵吵知道吗?
Right
我们不敢了
- Move, quick - Thank you
- 开车走吧 快点呀 - 谢谢 谢谢
"Bull's Eye", here's a steak
打靶仔 这里有美国牛扒
Chocolate milk,
朱古力奶
pizza, all yours
还有意大利小菜你慢慢尝吧
Take care of your buddies
你要灵灵圣圣 保佑我们这班老朋友
We won't forget your share
我们发了以后 一定会预你一份的
We'll be at the jewelry shop at 9:55 am
明早9点55分 我们抵达珠宝 店现场
Action at 10:00, for 5 minutes
十点钟展开行动 五分钟内搞掂
We'll split at 1 0:05
十点零五分撤退
Return here by 1 0:30
二十五分钟之后返回这里
I'll deliver the cargo
那就去交货收钱
Take you to Da Da at 1 1 :30
十一点半我会带你们去大大
The shop that has all
什么东西都有得卖的那间大大公司
Right?
对吗?
20% discount on Sunday
我也知道 礼拜日一百元当125元用
Blockhead
乌蝇头
Chung, Ah Sheung
八中 到时候我会通知阿嫦
will be at Da Da
在大大公司门口等你
It's up to you
至于她跟不跟你回去
to call
就要靠你自己打电话给她
We'll have two hours to shop
我们有两小时时间买东西
We'll be on board by 1 :30
一点半钟在青衣岛上船
With the money
那么大财就可以到手了
What do you think, Chubby?
肥姑 你有什么意见?
Alright
没有
Take a rest now
好 你们吃完后就睡片刻
We'll go through the plan late
晚上我会详细的跟你们谈谈整个计划
Taking us out
东哥 今晚休息抖足精神
tonight, Tung
总可以带我们去见识一下了
Remember our rules, Rooster?
生鸡 你再破坏就请你立即离队
Why's it closed, Chubby?
姑哥 怎么关了门的呀?
Damn, Indian trooper
糟啦 印度兵呀
Security guard
不是印度兵 是护卫队
That's reserved unit
护卫队?即是民兵
Get lost, open up
走开走开 开闸
Shut up
不许嘈呀
Sorry, sir
对不起 阿Sir
First job, right?
你是不是第一次呀?对不对?
Yes,
我是第一次
I've been out for a week
我刚出狱还不够一个礼拜
Who're your partners
讲 几个人呀?
I'm alone,
我是独行侠
can't you tell
不然我也不会让你们抓到
Go ask
你不相信的话
your inspector
就打电话给你们的大帮李洛夫
He knows me well
我衰都衰十几简给他
Stop the fancy stuff
你这人都甚为嚣张呀
2369, something's funny with that car
二三六九 那架车有点可疑
Send in some guys
叫便衣跟我来
Yes, Sir
是 黑仔 你们跟我来
Darkie, follow me
跟住我 跟住我走
This way, follow me
他们有枪的呀
They're armed
上车 全部上车
Get in, get in!
乌蝇头没有上车呀
Where's Blockhead?
乌蝇头去了哪里?
Where's he?
不要理他了 开车
Forget it, get going
乌蝇头没有上车呀
Where's Blockhead?
控制中心!
Everything's falling apart
穿和吃的好不好 都是整定的
The money
眼看大财就要滚进来
was right there
岂料又被那冤鬼破坏
Forget,
算了吧 总比打靶仔他们
we're better off than Bull's Eye
辛辛苦苦搏命只不过是吃白菜
You stupid, Blockhead
你这死乌蝇头 人家去东你就跑去西
Who do you think you are?
扮蟹一样的横行霸道
Well...you don't agree?
看…有什么好看呀?
You're a blacksheep
不是吗 正一是害人精
You're jinx
每次有你的份总是不吉利的
What do you want, bugger?
死仆街 你想怎么样?
What? For real?
什么?来真的?
Come on!
来就来好了
Bull's Eye's on my side
你看打靶仔帮我还是帮你好了
You creep, Bull's Eye
死把靶仔
How do you feel, Chubby?
肥姑 今天那单你的看法是怎么样?
Lucky to be alive
今天是不幸中的大幸
We're all here. That's what counts
最紧要的是大家平安
We've been through fire and rain
我们这班自己老友有什么场面没见过
We're still with you
东哥 你作主好了
We'll act according to plan
我的意思是照样去做
Their security will loosen up
今天这班印度人抓到盲炳后
After the action this morning
他们的警惕性一定会放松
We'll give them an encore
我就弄个回马枪给他们尝尝
We'll operate in three days
我们三天之后再来一次
We'll act in unison from now
由今天开始大家一致行动
All for one, right?
齐出齐入 好不好?
Every cloud has a silver lining
真是柳暗花明了 哈哈
So we have three days
照我的想法有三天在这里的话
Time to relax with some girls
当前的急务就是找女人来玩玩
I've heard of
人家说香港按摩院搞到春光无边
the massage parlours here
有声有色
Must give a try
我也没有试过
Lovely girls they have
还有三温暖 什么小姐陪酒
Roosters, don't start up again
生鸡 你又在搞破坏呀?
Start up what?
什么搞破坏呀?
Can't stand
再这样谷下去
another day like this
没火出就不坏也要坏了
What's most precious, Blockhead?
乌蝇头 你说做人最宝 贵是什么?
Freedom
自由
Right, freedom
不错 是自由呀
You must get some
姑哥 等一会你开声跟东哥争取
freedom for us
一致出外过瘾
I'll back you up
到时我一定帮你讲好话
I've been thinking
我已经想清楚了 当前最急的是钱
What we need is to relax
大家去找女人贺埠
Right, Roosters?
生鸡 你说对不对?
Do you mean it?
东哥 今天有着落真的还是假的?
Chung, go see Ah Sheung
八中 你也很想见见嫦女是吗?
Let's go out together tonight
那么我们就一齐去好了
Terrific
好
Tung
东哥
Please wait, we're working
先坐一会 我正在做工作呀
Take a seat
坐
998, Ah Lam
九九八 小兰
Shameless
嗳 不害臊
Tai, this is Tung
喂 阿泰呀 我是大东呀
You're at the Crimson Kid?
现在你在红孩儿呀?
I'll be right there
好 我马上来
Tell me when I'm there
见了面再说 就这样吧
Ah Sheung
阿嫦
I'm here first, who's in charge
我先来的 守守秩序 谁是负责人?
Stop arguing, take your turn
不要嘈了 轮住来嘛
Who's first, desert rat?
谁先来的呀?沙漠九
- Ah Sheung - Tung
- 嫦女 - 东哥
- Chung - Ah Sheung
- 八中 - 阿嫦
You've changed so much
你很摩登 差点儿不认识你
You've gained weight
你也胖了点
You said you worked at a night club
你不是说过在夜总会做的吗?
Yes, at night
是 晚上呀 晚上才上班夜总会
I share this place with Lulu daytime
白天跟露露分租这里 分上下班
I've bought
对了
your favorite food
刚才我出去买了点你喜欢吃的小菜
- Stay for dinner - Alright
- 今天晚上在这里吃饭吧 - 好
Bring in some pops, Monkey
猴子 拿两罐汽水进来
Took you so long to call
你覆机迟不迟一点呀
I'm with someone, call you later
我现在正在见客 迟点给你电话
Well, that's life
没办法 劳碌命呀
Thanks
麻烦你 谢谢
Where's the goods?
那些货呢?
Some unexpected thing happened
今天那单买卖出了意外
Should've called me earlier
你为什么早不通知我呀?
I'm telling you now
我来的目的就是告诉你
We postpone for 2 days
过两天后我就会交货
Tung,
大东呀 好惨呀
I'm only the middle man
你明明知道我是做中间人
I've promised to deliver tonight
我答应人家今天晚上交货的呀
Forget it then
那么就算好了
Easy, let's talk about it
不要太冲动 坐下来慢慢的谈谈
Pops, boss
大哥 汽水呀
- Where's Dong? - At the sauna
- 阿唐呢? - 阿唐去了新大华冲凉
Call him back
马上叫他回来
He took in this forged $1,000 bill
他验也没验过就收了一张假金牛回来
He's going to take in anything
他快要连溪钱也收回来了
Dong said needed an Ultra-violet light
阿唐说过该安装紫外光灯验水印的了
That's what he thinks
谁都知道阿妈是女人
I can tell by just looking,
他一双眼我也一双眼
so should he
我一望就知真与假
Next time
你告诉他下次再收到这种假金牛
he'll swallow it
我就要他吞下去
- Understand? - Understand
- 明白了没有? - 明白
- Boss - Out
- 大哥 - 滚出去
Tung, have a drink
东哥 菊花茶呀
See, these rookies are worthless
你说说看 现在的青年真是气死人
I haven't lost weight on them though
幸亏气来气去我都没瘦
You said in two days, eh?
你刚才说过两天是吗?
That's fine with me
两天就两天好了
But, my buddies need bread
不过 我要招呼那班弟兄
Advance some money to me first
想跟你先拿几万块钱
Alright, boss?
大哥 没事吧
We're all
大家在江湖上
brothers
没烧过黄纸都算好弟兄
We're from different clans
千万不要分桂枝仔和大圈仔
But we're brothers nevertheless
最紧要是要讲义气
Share and share all, how much?
有钱的话大家用 你要多少?
$30,000 for deposit
就当作预支三万吧
Let's do it this way
不如这样吧 不要当作预支
I've a problem,
我有件事给人累得很惨
can you help?
你帮不帮我的忙?
What about?
什么事?
This guy sold me out
有个二五仔
several times
害了我几次害到我鸡毛鸭血一样
You can have the $30,000,
我现在拿三万块钱出来
extra
作为我招呼你的弟兄们
Just finish this guy off
你们替我杀了他
What's his background
有没有手尾的呀?
He is public enemy
没有 这个二五仔得罪人多过吃饭
You're doing everyone a favor
仇家多到算不清
A big favor for me
你就算帮我一个忙吧
OK
好
I'll do it for $50,000
五万块钱我帮你搞掂他
Now you're talking
好兄弟 好兄弟
Welcome, Merry X'mas
欢迎欢迎 圣诞快乐
Welcome, sirs
欢迎老板 欢迎老板
Come in, sirs
几位呀 老板?请里面坐
Indian Troopers again
又是印度兵来的
The ladies are here
小姐来了
This is Jo Jo, sit down
这个叫祖祖 祖祖坐下来
- This is Di Di - Hi, boss
- 这个叫D.D.坐 - 老板
Why standing, sit down
各位老板 为什么站着不坐呀?
Make yourself at home
不要这么好礼貌了 坐下慢慢谈吧
Please sit down
先坐下吧
Sorry,
真不好意思
your lady is with another guest
刚才你叫那位小姐正在坐
She'll be here in a while
等一会她会过来跟你打招呼的
This is Joel, enjoy yourselves
这位祖儿小姐 你们好好的聊聊呀
Why so quiet?
为什么不说话呀?
You stood me up last time
恨你呀 为什么上次甩我底呀?
Something came up
突然之间有事嘛
Why didn't you call?
为什么不用传呼机叫我?
You knew I worked here
明知我过了场也不来找我
You're hooked on me
是不是牵记我呀?
Yes, with a hanger
对 用衣架把你挂起来
Joel, telephone
祖儿 先去听电话
Sorry
对不起了这位先生
Helen is here
海儿过来跟你打个招呼
Vow, sharp looking chick
哗 这个妞比刚才那个好多了
This is Ah Sheung, stupid
什么?你傻了吗?她就是阿嫦呀
- Ah Sheung? - Rooster
- 阿嫦吗? - 生鸡
Ah Sheung? You're like a princess
是阿嫦呀?这么漂亮好像仙女一样
Ah Sheung?
- 阿嫦? - 乌蝇头
Chubby
姑哥
I'm bored, let's dance
闷得要命 去跳舞去
Where're you going?
你去哪儿?不陪我呀?
Can you dance?
你会跳舞吗?
Drink
喝酒吧
Have to pee. Coming?
好 先去厕所小个便 一齐好吗?
OK, all for one
好 一致行动
Luxurious
这么豪华呀
- More so then our Eastern Hotel - Sure thing
- 比东方宾馆还要好 - 当然
Thanks
谢谢
Have to pay to pee
小便也要给钱的吗?
How much then?
不知给多少才行呀
$5 to pee, $10 to shit
小便五块 大便十块
$10 for two, right?
先生 我们两人十块钱对不对?
Thanks, care to wash up?
谢谢 洗手 洗手
See, I've told you
我跟你说的 对不对呀?
Here you are
你们两位这间
Well, good night
这间是我的 早点睡吧兄弟们
Go ahead
你先上吧
So grand,
这里真豪华
very proper for your class
这里才可配衬你这么高级的小姐
- Have to pee first - Corny
- 让我先小便 - 老土
Let me rub you back
替你擦背
I'll be on TVB's
我下星期日参加无线翡翠台的
Sing Sing Sing
星声星呀
Here a preview for you
我现在优先唱给你听好不好?
Great, terrific
好听 好听…
I haven't started yet
我还没唱你就说好听
It hurts
好痛呀 不要这么大力嘛
I'll sing now
我现在唱给你听呀
"Let happiness graces upon me"
让快乐为我展开
"It's joyful to be with you"
和你共叙原是可爱
"I beg you to let me go"
求求你让我躲开
"Cause there's no future for us"
明知跟你没将来
"No future for us"
没将来
"You're like a rat pack"
那么多人一齐来呀 老土到极
I'm a respectable lady
你不要面子但我要面子呀
Everybody else does it
别人都是这个样子的
I'm different,
我怎可以跟她们比呀
I'm no whore
我不是奉旨陪人睡觉的
I have a very
我虽然走出来是有点难看
good reputation
但没人不认得我是贝茜
My customers
许多客人捧了我几个月场
know my rules
我理也不理他们 神经病
But you have agreed to come to watch TV
是你自己说肯开房和看电视的嘛
Right, let's watch TV
看嘛 不是在看电视吗?
Stay naked and watch TV, that's your choice
你自己老土 脱光衣服来看
I'd paid
我买了出街钟了
for your time
我大哥说买了钟就什么都搞掂了
How much, a hundred thousand
掂?掂你的死人头 十万八千七吗?
I'm not in the mood
大小姐不喜欢就什么情趣都没有了
What am I to do
现在我怎么办?
Watch TV then I'll leave first
怎办?你看电视 或者是我先走
A mahjong game is waiting
我还约了几个姐妹打麻将呢
God damn it
看看看 看你的死人头
I don't have all night
你知不知道我没有时间了
Time flies
眼睛一眨又几年了
Now you lead a fast life
你现在过的是灯红酒绿
Remember when we were back home
你记不记得下放的时候做知趸
We lived like dogs
我们干活干到连狗都不如呀?
I was good at nothing
记得
You helped me a lot
那时候我样样都不行都是靠你帮我
Sheung, I'll be rich in a few days
阿嫦 过几天我就发达了
I can't read your mind
我不知你的想法如何?
If you still feel for me
如果你对我还有感情的话
Then go back with me
我想带你回去享享福
Back home?
返广州?
I'll have a lot of money soon
过几天我就有很多钱了
We'll buy a house and get married
我们可以回去买地 做房子和结婚
Goodbye poverty then
我和你根本就不用再挨苦了
What's up?
喂 怎么样?
Tomorrow? What time?
明天?几点钟?
Six-thirty
六点半
Alright
好
Tai Koo City, alright
在太古城 就这样吧
Telephone for you, Fatso
狗哥 你的电话
Telephone, Fatso
狗哥 狗哥 你的电话呀
Who is it?
谁在找肥狗呀?
It's me, Tai
狗哥 我是阿泰呀
Tai?
阿泰呀?
What is it this time?
你这臭小子 有什么新的资料呀
Good stuff, coming?
我有些好资料 你现在出来
- Where? - Tai Koo City
- 在哪里? - 我在太古城
Tai Koo City is a huge place
太古城你包办好了
Shopping Centre
不是 我现在在太古城商场 你马上出来
I'll be there after supper
好 我吃完饭就来
Stop it, Fatso
不要搞呀 狗哥
- Bye, sweetie - Bye
- 靓女 拜拜 - 拜拜
- Are they here yet? - Over there
- 来了没有 - 来啦 在那边
- Over there? - Yes
- 就是这批人呀? - 是呀
- Go say hello - Me?
- 过去打个招呼 - 又要我去?
Of course, who else?
当然是你去 难道要我去吗?
- Why me? - Move
- 每次都是我去 - 去吧
Tung, where're your buddies?
东哥 你那班弟兄在哪里?
Three dollars
三块钱
Sweet young thing
很漂亮呀 长得很甜呀
Here's the change
找回七块
Go for drink after work?
几点收工呀 去喝茶去
I'll be busy
没空
You're shorter
你比他矮呀
Fatso
狗哥
You monkey, where's your boss?
你只死猴子 你的大哥去了哪儿呀?
My boss?
我大哥?
Ice-cream in the winter? Good for you
这么冷还吃雪糕 你身体真好呀
- Where are you going? - Fatso
- 你去哪里呀? - 肥狗
- Hi, Charlie - Robert, how's the case?
- 查理 - 罗拔 这案件怎么样了?
They're working around the clock
他们日以继夜的工作
This is Inspector Chan
这位是陈帮办
Nothing yet?
还没有消息吗?
Won't be long, sir
很快就有了
Those are the victim's family
他们是遇害者的家属
We'll take care of everything
不用伤心 一切交给我们
Tung
喂 东哥
Take it easy. It's me, Switch Blade
大东 别乱来呀 你认识我刀片华的
The boss is in Macau
我大哥去了澳门
Please, stop
不要这样 我不敢了
I'll call him down
我识该怎么做了
Boss, boss
我会帮你叫他下来 大哥 大哥
What's up?
什么事呀?
Tung is here
大圈仔的兄弟来找你了
I'm in Macau, remember?
叫你告诉他们说我去了澳门
Tai, my buddies are all here
阿泰 我们的弟兄全都在门外
I've told them
我答应过他们
if I couldn't find you.
五分钟之内找不着你的话
I'll fold this place up
我就扫平这里
He has a gun, boss
大哥 他带了一柄枪来呀
Take it easy, don't get mad.
你别乱来呀 你发神经呀
Listen,
你不要凶
I'm pretty good with the gun
我机关枪假假地都放过几百发
Come out fast
你快点出来
OK, I'll be right there
好 好 好 我现在下来
Mr Lam, sir
林Sir
Tai
阿泰
Mr Lam, Mr Lok, what a coincidence?
林Sir 陆Sir 怎么这么巧呀?
Our boss
就这巧
invites you for tea
我们警司想你到写字楼喝杯奶茶
I'll go later, OK
迟一点我自己去可以吗?
Fatso was murdered
你知不知道肥狗给人杀了
I've heard,
是 是 我刚在收音机里听到
that's life
一个人真的化了
Our boss like to talk to you about it
我们警司为了这件事想亲自和你谈谈
You and Fatso were very close
因为肥狗生前与你谈得很投机
But...
不过我…
Move, or else the handcuffs...
走吧 用到手铐大家都不好了
Stop kidding around
别拿这些东西来讲笑好吗?
- It's alright - Move
- 没事了 走吧 - 谢谢 谢谢
How's the tea
怎么样?香片行不行呀?
Great stuff
行 很香呀
Is Fatso's tea
对喔 肥狗的
That's his cup
是肥狗生前剩下来的茶叶冲的
Bot bad
没有坏掉
When did you see him last?
你最后什么时候见过他呀?
- Who? - Fatso
- 谁呀? - 肥狗
A few weeks ago
几个星期了
You're his informer,
你是肥狗的线人
who wants him dead?
他最近跟谁过不去呀?
I don't know
不知道
You cops have a lot of enemies
当警察的人是最多仇家的 对吗?
Just kidding, just kidding
我讲笑的讲笑的
You deal with the 'O' gang,
你是不是跟很多大圈仔有来往的
right?
对吗?
That was history
这是以前的事
Who killed Fatso?
你知不知道是谁杀肥狗的?
I don't know, I only worked for him
不知道 我是帮肥狗做事的
I have nothing to tell you
没有必要讲这么多的事给你们知道
We'll charge you
肥狗已经死了 你隐瞒事实就是帮凶
I'm no murderer. I've been helpful
我没有杀人 我帮你们就多了
Check the record
不相信的话你们去查查看
No need
不用查了
Tai
阿泰 你知不知道
A murdered cop is something else
杀死一个警察的后果是多严重
Lee, long time no see
李Sir 好久没见… 气色不错呀
Homicide takes care
一般谋杀案
of all murder cases
警方会交给凶杀组缉拿凶手
An unsolved case
如果抓不到凶手的话
usually fades away
一年半载就会松弛了
Sometimes it would be forgotten altogether
或者有些人会忘记
But a murdered cop
但是杀死一个警察
The whole police force is on the case
现在全香港的警察都在追查中
Every cop involved
每个有份调查的伙计
is trying extra hard
都不计较如何辛苦
The case is to be solved
或者有没有O.T.都要查个水落石出
A year, 1 0 years,
一年 十年 一百年
a life time may be
所有当警务人员都不会忘记这件事
I've said enough
我不多讲 你心里明白
Co-operate with us,
唯一保障你自己的利益
that's your only choice
就是跟我们合作
Tell me, who killed Fatso?
你告诉我 谁杀死肥狗的?
I swear to the gods,
我可以对灯火发誓
Fatso and I were brothers
肥狗和我有如亲兄弟
If he was sick, I felt the pain
平时他头昏了 我就有点像发烧了
I feel so bad now
这次他遇害 我都很伤心
This is no funeral home,
不要哭了 这儿是警察局
stop it
你以为是殡仪馆吗
Here's the 'O' gang file,
这里有八个大圈仔
pick them out
你跟我找四个出来
Unfamiliar faces,
很陌生
can't recognize anyone
有一两个是见过一面但没什么印象
Listen loud and clear
我讲得很清楚 如果你找不到凶手
Tell us or your business is done with
我保证一个月之内把你的架步扫光
We'll wipe out your gang in a month
赶绝你班马仔
This is only guess work
李Sir 我是大约猜想的
Contact us daily
你每日跟我们用电话联络
Brief us the latest news
有消息就马上报上来 知道吗?
For sure, for sure
一定 一定
More,
还有
there are $200,000 award money
杀肥狗和银行枪战两案能破的话
That,
有二十万花红
plus your own savings
连你自己的阴功钱加在一起
Will feed you for life
就够你过下半世了
Money doesn't mean a thing
不要讲钱 自己人
Now get out
走吧
See you, gentlemen
各位阿Sir 再见了
- Follow him - Yes, sir
- 找人去跟踪他 - 是
If I guess right,
如果我估计没错的话
these are the ones
检查一下这四张
Yes, sir
是
The sale is slow
现在的车真是淡市呀
What sale?
什么车呀?
Used cars, gloomy
二手车呀 有价无市 没有前途
Yes, gloomy
对 没前途
Your gun, sir, is sticking out
这位阿Sir 你的手枪凸了出来
Beat you up
打死你
No, please, don't
不要呀 不要这样呀…
Don't
别这样呀…
Let me tell you why you have to die
我想你明白一下自己为什么会死
You opportunist
你做得太过不清不楚了
You cheated us to kill the cop
叫我们杀死那个警察
And you sold us out to the police
又到警察局去把我们告密
We only live once
我们大圈仔一条是命 两条也是命
Tung, I didn't say anything
东哥 不要这样 我没爆出你们的事
Don't, I didn't say anything
不要这样 我真的没有爆呀
No difference. I'll take that you did
你讲什么都无所谓 我就当你爆
Stop, please don't
不要呀 不要这样呀…
Tung, stop!
东哥 不要呀
Help...
救命呀…
We are old friends
我跟你是老朋友呀
Don't, I kept my mouth shut
不要这样呀 我没爆你的事呀
We won't put out the next one
这次一点起火就不会熄灭的
What did you say to the cops?
你跟那些警察讲过什么?讲
Stop crying
你不要哭 不许哭
Shut up
闭嘴
My mistake
我错了
I was wrong
阿东 我错在太赏识你了
to think so high of you
我太看得起了你 阿东
I wanted you
是 我叫你杀肥狗存心想你入局
to join me
同你做弟兄
Your guts and my brain, fine team we are
以我的智 你的勇 一齐打天下
I didn't talk
在警局里警察打我迫我吃屎
even under torture
我也没有爆出来
So put on the fire now,
你不信就算好了
go ahead
你烧吧 烧好了 你烧死我好了
I believe in money only
我看在钱的份上 暂时不理真或假
Take with you $1,500,000 tomorrow
你明天十一点半带一百五十万元
To the Tsuen Wan Bus terminal
到荃湾巴士总站跟我换货
Come alone or don't come at all
如果你多带半个人就不用指望见到我
And we'll get you sooner or later
不过我迟早都会找到你 明白没有?
We're partners,
我一心一意想和你合作
what's the problem
怎么会有问题呀
The problem is yours
有问题 是你的问题
Everyone is against us
现在人家不单剃了我们的眼眉
Soon we'll be out in the cold
就快要连祖宗的山坟也要铲平了
The situation is clear
现在形势很清楚了
Time for action
是我们演身手的时候了
We must attack
我们一定要先发制人
Remember the Grand Hotel case
想当年新兴酒楼那桩事
The 3 of us over that rat pack
我们三个人斩到那些烂鬼一仆一碌
They would shake all over just to have my name
谁人听到泰哥的名就脚震了
We'll get them tomorrow
大哥
when they deliver
他们收货的时候对付他们
Terrific
好 马骝
Get some guns
你跟那班越南仔很熟识
from the Vietnam gang
马上去找十支八支枪回来
Well...now?
不过…马上?
Not tomorrow, not next year, now!
不是马上难道等到明年?
It's not that simple
大哥 东托西托问题就不大
I'll manage with a week or two
只要你给三五七天即是15日时间给我
That's more reasonable
我就可能搞得掂
Pay cash, money gets you anything
懵人 有现钱就有现货
Say, how much?
你讲 要多少钱呀?
Right, money can buy anything
说得对 有钱就可以使得鬼推磨
But then
不过 话得说回转来
We're going to lose...
大哥 我们是缸瓦 他们是瓷器
I mean they have nothing to lose
不 我们是瓷器 他们是缸瓦
It doesn't worth it
这样撼法值不值得?
But we got pushed
现在人家把我们赶绝
against the wall
我死了你们有什么好处
You all talk big,
平时每个人张牙舞爪
now's time to prove it
有事就变作缩头乌龟
Switch Blade, tell it to them
刀片华 你说 你告诉他们
Tai is our boss, we're his gang
是 泰哥是大哥 我们是好兄弟
We're here
这么多年来追随着泰哥出生入死
to serve him as always
有没有推过宕过
But I suggest to stay cool this time
但是这一次我也赞成要冷静
Those guys are beasts
那些大圈仔没人性的 他们没有根基
We've our
我们家在香港
families here
奋斗到今时今日总算安居乐事
We must think for them
我们是不是要为手足的妻儿子女着想
Right?
对不对?
Boss, stay cool please
泰哥 你要冷静一点
Can't we stay up for a while?
大哥 先拖住一会行不行?
Or take a hike
或者离开一段时间作战略上的退却
to buy time
可不可以呢?
It's only my second bowl
我只是第二碗
We'll do as you say, fantastic
照你们的意思去做 你们真棒
That's the New Year man,
这个就是新年老人
come out at X'mas
一到耶诞这家伙就四处游行了
It's Christmas
耶诞呀
This is our
喂 各位老板
Iast day in Hong Kong.
今日是我们在香港的最后一天
Whatever undone
大家有什么心事未了的话
should be taken care of
就速速了却它
But don't stay up too late
不过不要太晚呀
Let's go, all for one
我开车 大家一致行动
Satisfied, Rooster?
生鸡 基本上你满意了吗?
What a guy
东哥 你真是通情达理了
Move, move
去 去啦
And then?
跟着是什么?
We'll stay up the night
今天晚上每人都不准回家 玩通宵
Why didn't you
大东 你真坏
come up
来到这里也不上来找我
Just not in the mood
明天我又要出门 所以没心情
You're always like this
你整天都是这个样子
How about your customers
怎么样?没熟客人吗?
Bunch of bores
那些客人闷死人了
Quit early tonight, go home.
回去截钟 早些回家睡觉吧
That much
这么多钱?
It's New Year
给你过节用嘛
When will you be back?
你什么时候回来呀?
All a week,
大概一星期左右
I'll call you
我回来就用传呼机叫你
- Don't tease me - I won't
- 不要骗我呀 - 不会
Bye
拜拜
Keep the stub, there's a lucky draw
下星期日罗浩楷来抽奖
First prize is a trip to Pattaya
头奖是去芭提雅五日游 包食宿
All yours, I have no use of it
我要来没有用 全都送给你
Really?
是不是呀?真的?
- I won't be here - Really?
反正我们已不在香港了
Where's Pattaya, Rooster?
生鸡 芭提雅在哪里?
Pattaya? Oh USA
芭提雅?在美国呀
USA
美国
Merry Christmas
李Sir Merry Christmas
You really going tomorrow?
你们决定明天走了?
Why don't
其实你自己可以留下来
you stay?
大不了少点外出
Come with me
我都希望你跟我回去
May be you'll like it here
或者住下去你会习惯香港生活
I didn't like it
好像我一样
here at first
开始时我都心灰意冷差点返回广州
I've grown accustom to it now
不过捱到今时今日 虽然是辛苦一点
I'm my own
但是我喜欢吃什么有什么
boss here
穿什么有什么
May be you'll miss
就算你现在要我返去广州
this place too
也不一定适应
It's not a matter
这不是我喜不喜欢留在这里的问题
of wanting to stay or not
而是整体的问题
If I get caught,
如果我留在这里被人抓了去
everyone's in trouble
就等于全部抓了去
I must go
我一定要返回去
We shouldn't discuss it anymore
如果你不走的话我们无谓再讨论
There's no time
根本没有时间了
It's for you
送给你的
Buy yourself some goodies
这两千块给你买唇膏用的
Take good care of yourself
我明天就要走了 你要保重呀
When are you coming back?
你何日再回来呀?
Difficult to say,
我都不知道 很难讲的
give me a kiss
来 让我吻一吻
What are you doing?
干什么呀你?
Be your lover
跟你做情人
You agreed to come out
我跟你说过讲明是吃宵夜的
But not here, I don't like it
又带了我到这种地方 我不高兴的
My friends have all made it
我的老友们已经全部上马了
And I'm here talking
我依然还没有 你究竟想怎么样?
I want to go dancing with you
我想晚晚同你去的士高跳舞
And then go shopping
然后去公司买衣服
I might not be back
我自己都不知道回不回来香港的
Alright, $10,000
行 一万块钱
$10,000?
一万块?
What? Doesn't worth it?
什么?不值吗?
You, $10,000?
你值一万块?
Or do you want to watch TV?
要嘛这样 你在这儿看电视
There's a film on, from Taiwan
这套是国语长片 是台湾片来的
You haven't seen it for sure
你一定没有看过
I'll give you ten, where would you like it?
好 我就给十粒你 你喜欢我打那儿
I'm no fancy guy I know
我是大圈仔 不识ABC 做事没情趣
You took me as a fool
跟你讲心你当我是烂袋
But what are you, pumpkin
你是什么?你是烂番茄 鸡仔饼
Strip off, now
马上脱衣服
Quick
快
Chewing gum
- 香口胶 - 吞了
Come here
过来
Stay down
趴下
Don't, don't
不要 不要呀
I picked up
这盒带我用尽千辛万苦
this tape for $40,000
花了四万元才找到回来的
This 'O' gang
这班大圈仔真是太离谱
is too much
简直瞧不起香港的警察
They are just dirt back home
在大陆又不见他们有这样威风
Enough evidence to go to court?
不知够不够证据上法庭呀?
Hong Kong
我们国家什么时候
is something else
才会有如香港那样现代化
And...Tung
其实…东哥 如果留在香港
Can't we stay at all?
是不是真的没办法可想呢?
Now you too, Chubby?
肥姑 怎么连你都不想回去?
Just reflecting their view
只不过反映大家兄弟的意见嘛
I don't understand
其实我真的不明白
in fact
你为什么一定要我们走
They won't understand
他们几个不一定明白
Let me be honest with you
我不怕老实告诉你
I'm one of the most
香港警察当局把我列为十大通缉犯
wanted persons here
无人能担保我
Now it's all on nothing
唯一的办法就是尽地一煲
With money I can hide out or a few years
然后返回内地匿藏几年
That's why we all have to go back
所以今次的计划就是大家都要走
Will you support me
我希望你支持我
All for one, one for all
总之我们要团结一致 枪口对外
Just like old time,
我和你就好像当年旗派战友一样
comrades
并肩作战
But we have the advantage this time
不过今次我们就占尽优势
Goodbye, honey
亲爱的 拜拜
Merry Christmas
圣诞快乐
One more kiss
多吻一次
What so funny?
笑 笑什么?印度兵
You are
笑你呀
Can't I help you?
先生 想买点什么?随便看看好了
Bring in the cheque
你把支票先拿进来给我
Anything you like
先生想买点什么?
A necklace
我想买条链给…
For you girlfriend
买条链给女朋友是吗?
- No, my lover - Pardon?
- 不 送给我爱人的 - 什么?
No, for my wife. Those please
不 送给我女人的 拿那些来看看
This one?
这条呀?
Some new ones over there
那边还有些新款的
What's up?
干什么?
It's a stick up. Don't move
打劫呀 不许动
It's a stick up, down
打劫呀 蹲下
It's a stick up...
打劫呀 打劫呀
Don't move, hands over heads
不许动 手放上头 想死吗…
Want to die?
不许动 谁动就先打谁
Don't watch, down...
不许看 看什么?趴下…
Don't scream!
不要吵!
Don't shot...
不要开枪…
Open up the safe, quick
开保险箱 锁匙 快点快点
Don't look
不许望
Down, stay down
蹲下 蹲下呀
Don't scream or want to die
不要吵…你们想死吗?
Let's go, Blockhead
乌蝇头 走啦 走啦…快!
Not me, I didn't press it
不是我按的 不是我按
Shit...out from back door
快!快! 不行了…后面走吧!
Freeze, or I'll shoot
不许动 谁动就先打谁 不许动…
Don't move
别动!
Don't away, wanna get shot?
看什么?还要看 想打靶是吗?
Split
撤退
Get going
走 走呀
Don't chase!
不许追
Stay down
走 不许追来
Those guys called me just now, sir
李Sir 刚才那班大圈仔call我
They want me back
说不在这儿交易
at Crimson Kid
叫我回到红孩儿那儿等他们电话
There's a leak on your side
会不会是你们那儿走漏风声呀
S.P. calling Steve, S.P. calling Steve
S.P. call史提夫 S.P. call史提夫
Steve's here, sir
收到了 阿Sir
Put a transmitter in Tai's car
你现在马上放个通讯器在阿泰车上
- And bring the car over - Roger
- 然后开架车子过来 - 是
We're putting a transmitter in your car
我现在安装个通讯器在你车上
Keep in touch on your way
你在路上跟我们保持联络
What transmitter?
什么通讯器呀?
It's unreliable
发射这样东西是不可靠的
I might lose contact
万一我和你失去联络…
Trust us, go now
去吧 对我们要有信心才行
Take care of me, sir
李Sir 你要照顾住我呀…
Test, Test, over
Test test over
1,2,3, do you read me
一二三 三二一 收到没有 收到没有
Over
Over
Nice and clear, relax
收得很清楚 不用太紧张
State your position
报告一下你自己的位置
Looks like Cornwall street
这里好像是歌和老街
Right, I see the Baptist Hospital
对 对 我看见浸会医院了
Tung, you're like a ghost
东哥 你真是神出鬼没了
That's not funny
你要拿这种东西来开玩笑
Tung's car appeared
大圈仔的车突然出现
from nowhere, over
叫我跟着他们的车尾 Over
Do you read me, over
收不收到呀 Over
I knew it. I knew it
我一早就说靠不住的嘛
Over, Over...
Over Over…
I'm somewhere
我现在不知在老虎岩
in Tiger Hill
或是横头磡山水塘顶上面 好像…
Nice job, eh!
一切顺利吧 辛苦了
Congratulations, Tung
东哥 恭喜你了
I take it myself
我自己拿好了
Right, how do we celebrate?
好 怎样去庆祝一下呀?
How about
东哥 天气冷了
the hot-pot
去吃一顿沙爹火锅好吗?
I know a joint in Mongkok
我的手下在旺角开了一间馆子
Tung, found this in his car
东哥 这颗东西是在他车上搜到的
Micro-wave amplifier
是超音波呀 车内收音机的扩音器
Transmitter
追踪器
Look, aren't we buddies
不 喂 我们是不是兄弟呀
Don't frame me with this
别拿这颗东西来硬要我承认呀
Where are you now Tai? Over
阿泰 现在那班大圈仔怎么样?Over
Please don't, Tung, Tung, I'm sorry, I so sorry
不…东哥 我不敢了 我错了…
Please spare me
我求求你不要打死我呀
AS calling HQ,
A.S.叫总部指挥部
Tiger Hill reservoir
目的地是老虎岩水库
Come in please, over
立即到现场 Over
Listen you, you're surrounded
下面的人听着 你们已经被包围了
Put down your weapons and surrender
立即放下所有武器 举手投降
Tung, they forced me
东哥 现在没有时间解释了
to co-operate
是警局迫我和他们合作
No use to kill me
你杀死了我也没有用的
Take me hostage,
你把我押出去做人质
bargain with them
我做挡箭牌好了 东哥
Alright, talk with them
好 你出去和他们谈谈
You'll be the first to go
如果他们阻拦我们 你第一个就没命
Blockhead
乌蝇头
No funny stuff
不许动 一动就要你的命
Don't shoot
不要开枪呀
Get in
准备上车 快点
This is the last warning
现在是最后警告
I'll count down
我数五下之内你们还不投降
from 5
我会使用武力
It's me Tai,
是我呀 阿泰呀
I'm their hostage
李Sir 我被人胁持住呀
Don't shoot
你不要开枪呀 我没命的
Do you hear?
你听不听见我讲呀?
-It's me, Tai - 5, 4, 3, 2...
五 四 …
- Stop counting please. -... 1!
- 我呀 阿泰呀… - 三 二 一
Stop it
你还数…
Fire
开火
Get away from the car
离开车子 离开车子
Over here Blockhead
乌蝇头 乌蝇头过来呀
It's going to explode
这车就要爆了
Hold on
顶住呀你
Blockhead can't make it, help him
乌蝇头不行了 帮手扶着他
Blockhead can't make it
乌蝇头 乌蝇头不行了 快点
Go there!
带几个伙记去那边
Go!
走呀!
Tung
大东
Doctor Ngam, please help us
颜医生 又要麻烦你了
Come in, can't talk here
先进来 这里讲话不方便
Tell them to go
你叫他们走吧
I can't
怎么办 不行的
You've passed the written exams
你这样辛苦才过了两次考试
Oral exam is next week
下个星期就要面试了
They're going to ruin your hope
你这样帮助他们不但拿不到医生牌
And we have to go to jail
还要连累我们坐监呀
Think for yourself, old man
你几十岁人了 有没有考虑清楚呀
He's passed out, doctor
颜医生 他晕倒了
Coming
来了 你快去买葡萄糖盐水
Go get some antibiotics
和抗生素回来 去吧
What's your name
贵姓
I can't tell you
不方便讲你知
Just tell her
你就替我传呼告诉她
A good friend called
是她一位好朋友传呼就行了
Phone number please
电话号码?电话几号?
Phone number? Area code 3
电话?电话号码是区字头三字
Hurry
快点进去
Sorry, madam
嫂嫂 对不起
Is this 843907
喂喂 你们那儿是不是843907呀
Ah Sheung, it's me
阿嫦 是我呀
- Are you alright? - Alright, we're alright
- 你们有没有事呀? - 没事 没事
You're a genius, doc, all 3 are out.
医生真棒呀 三颗全都拿出来了
Wait, there's one near the heart
等一等 还有一颗子弹头在心脏附近
Can't do it here
我这里没办法做手术
Has to go to a hospital
一定要政府医院才行
Sheung, we're not going
阿嫦 我们不走了 不用走了
- I've called - What?
- 我打了电话了 - 什么?
I've called the police
我报了警了
Can we talk, doctor
颜医生 出来商量一下
Coming
来了
What's the odds doing it here?
如果把子弹头拿出来 危险性有多大
Impossible
不可能
You took the rest out
刚才那几颗不是拿出来了吗?
Not this one, not here
现在在这环境之下 不行也得行呀
It's right by the heart
现在这颗子弹在心脏侧边
We need blood, everything
现在这里输血 止血什么都没有
We'll kill him
如果不顾一切的拿出来
doing it here
造成大量出血死定了
It has to be a registered hospital?
那是不是一定要送去国家医院呢?
No underground clinics to do it?
有没有地下医院用不着惊动政府的呢
None
没有
Ah Sheung is coming over
阿嫦快要到这儿来
She has a
她有个客人做医生的追求她
surgeon customer
或者会有办法
How are you, Blockhead?
乌蝇头 你怎么样了?
Don't leave me
你们不要把我留下呀
We're not
没人说要走
Ieaving
我们大家都不走陪你到底
Send him to hospital please
颜医生 麻烦你送他到医院
Just say he bumped into here
你就说他是上门求医的
Take a rest, Blockhead
乌蝇头 你安心休养
We'll send your share to your wife
我会把你的一份留起来交给嫂嫂的
We trust you
我们大家做了这么久的兄弟
to keep quiet
我相信你不会供出我们
No way, can't leave him alone
不可能 留下乌蝇头一个人在香港
All for one, remember
怎能算是团结一致 枪口对外呀
Chubby, what do you think?
肥姑 你说怎么办?
Chung
八中 你呢?
I've told Ah Sheung. I would be staying
我刚才跟阿嫦说过我暂时不走
Right, we all agree
对 对 基本上我们思想一致
It's up to you Tung,
走呀 你东哥说走就走好了
Iet's gamble
赌一下输赢
Or dump him into the ocean
不行就把他丢到大海里喂鱼好了
He's going
其实乌蝇头的身体怎能捱下去
to die
死定了
We're wasting time
其实讨论这个问题是多余的
We've told Chubby we would stay
我们早就跟姑哥讲过不走了
He'll die if we leave
你要他走等如要他死
Might as well shoot him now
不如你一枪打死他连他的那份也吞下
Blockhead, Blockhead
乌蝇头 乌蝇头
How's he?
怎么样?
He's dead
死了
Bury him please, doctor
颜医生 埋葬他
Take this
拿去吧
Mr. Lai, it's me, can't you tell?
黎先生 认不认识我呀?不认识我呀
Buddy, where's Old Man Street?
兄弟 请问你老人街在哪里?
- Straight ahead - Thanks
- 往前一直走 - 谢谢
Go home, keep off the street
没事不要在街上走来走去 返回家吧
Sorry, we're closing
不好意思 快些打烊 请合作
Keep of the street, Miss
小姐 不要逗留在街上
Stick back your heads
楼上的人无事不要把头伸出来
Everyone's familiar with the situation
各位 目前的情况明白吗?
Yes, sir
是 明白
One question, sir
阿Sir 我有一个问题
Yes, Mr Mchenzie
什么事 麦康士
How much warning do we give those bastards?
我们要警告他们多少次呀?
How much fucking warning will they give you?
你以为他们会给你多少次警告?
Shut up...bad guy's coming
别吵…衰人来了
Should come to church more often
应该多点来教堂 天主会保佑你
Look at our report
你看我们的那份报告
Had Wong Tai been sick lately?
黄泰最近有没有不精神?有没有病痛
Headache? Arthritis?
有没有头痛?有没有风湿?
1236, found anything?
一二三六 搜到没有?
Stop running, buddy
老友 你不要走
Stand still...you...
不要走…你
Quick!
快!
Stay there
不要出来
Don't move!
别动!
-Stand up, don't come close -Don't shot...
- 起身 不要过来 - 不要开枪
Don't kill him...
不要杀他…
Let's go!
走呀
Bring him go too!
带人质走
-Stand up, don't come close -Don't let the guy go
- 谁过来就死 - 不要放这个鬼佬
Don't shot...
不要开枪…
Let him go, let him go
放了他 放了他
Listen you over there
这是警察通告 前面的人听着
This is the Police Special Squad No.3
这是警察机动大队第三连
You are surrounded,
你们现在已经被全部包围
we're...
我们将会采取…
- Chung -That way!
- 八中 怎么样? - 走那边
Go first!
先走吧
Don't come near...
不要走过来 不要走过来呀
Don't come close...
不要走过来…
Don't you hear me. I'll kill him...
听不听到我说什么…我会打死他…
- Still come close - Shot!
- 还来… - 开枪
Chung, Chung
八中 八中
Chung
中…
Ah Sheung
阿嫦
Get up
起来
What's up, buddy?
什么事呀 老友?
- What's matter? - Well
怎么样?
What are you doing?
你们干什么呀?
It's full of cops outside
很多警察在外面呀 怎么办?
I'm still young, I don't want to die
我还年轻 我不想死
Chubby, let's surrender
姑哥 我们试试看投降吧
Tung, bargain with them
东哥 你试试看跟他们讲和吧
Is there a back door, doctor?
医生 你这里有没有后门呀?
There's a trap door up there
我们的阁仔上面有个暗门的
Get on the roof, it leads to Junction Road
出走瓦面直通出去就是联合道
Why didn't you say so?
你这臭八婆 早点说嘛
Wrong key
糟啦 这串锁匙不行
What key?
什么锁匙?
Key to this door
开这个门的锁匙弄错了 让我…
Stop
站住
What door?
什么门呀?
It isn't me, it isn't me
不关我的事 不关我的事
You called the police
是不是你报警出卖我们的?
Coming out now. He's armed
出来了 当心他有枪呀
Don't shoot, don't shoot
不要开枪 不要开枪呀
I'm a doctor,
我是医生
not the 'O' gang
我不是大圈仔 我是医生呀
Blow off the door
炸门
Go
上
Fire!
开火
Try bargain with them, Tung
东哥…试试看跟他们讲和
Keep quiet
嘘 不要嘈呀